<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- About Us -->
    <string name="aboutUsTitle1">About us</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody1">Resident Insure is an independent insurance company that offers an exclusive renters insurance program for the multi-family housing market. Teamed with several A-rated insurance carriers, we provide a great renters insurance program that will cover your personal belongings and liability coverage at competitive rates.</string>
    <string name="aboutUsSubtitle2">What is renters insurance?</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody2">Renters insurance is an insurance policy that provides monetary protection for your personal belongings against outside elements, i.e. fire, smoke, theft, water damage and explosion. Coverage for your personal belongings starts at $10,000 ($5,000 available in some states) with a maximum of $40,000 in coverage.</string>
    <string name="aboutUsSubtitle3">Is my personal property covered with this insurance policy?</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody3">In order for your personal possessions to be covered you must have at least a minimum selected under "Personal Contents" coverage e.g. $10,000. If you select "Liability Only" you will not have coverage for your personal possessions.</string>
    <string name="aboutUsSubtitle4">How do I get a quote and purchase a policy through Resident Insure?</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody4">Click the "Get a Quote" link in the main navigation to get a quote and enroll in a policy. You can also call us at (866) 249–1066 to get a quote and enroll with one of our representatives .In order to give you an accurate quote you will need to have your address, the name of your community where you reside, when you will be moving, and the names of all the adults living at that address.</string>
    <string name="getAQuote">Get a quote</string>
    <string name="aboutUsTitle5">Report a Claim</string>
    <string name="aboutUsSubtitle5">Markel American Policies</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody5">(800) 236–3113</string>
    <string name="aboutUsSubtitle6">QBE Policies</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody6">(800) 822–2997</string>
    <string name="aboutUsSubtitle7">Kemper Policies</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody7">(877) 586–8951</string>
    <string name="aboutUsSubtitle8">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="aboutUsBody8">(866) 249–1066 \nservice@residentinsure.com</string>


    <!-- Terms and conditions -->
    <string name="termsAndConditionsTitle1">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody1">These terms and conditions of use (these “Terms”) form a binding contract between Entrata Insurance Agency, LLC (“EIA”, “we”, “us”, “our”) and you (“you”, “your”).You acknowledge that you have read and understand these Terms and agree to conduct all transactions with us by electronic means, including electronic enrollment and payment. You understand that you are conducting an electronic transaction(s) and agree to use and receive communications through electronic means. You further agree to enter into any applicable insurance contract(s) electronically via the Internet, and to be notified regarding such insurance contract(s) via the same.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle2">1. Payment Terms.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody2">You agree, by submitting your payment information via this website, to authorize EIA to charge your credit card or debit your bank account for the amount(s) shown on such payment screens, which may include insurance premiums as well as administrative and other fees charged by EIA for its services (which EIA fees are non–refundable once collected, and are subject to change from time to time in EIA’s sole and reasonable discretion, without prior notice to you). For recurring debit transactions, you also authorize EIA to make automatic withdrawals between 3–15 days prior to the commencement of the next billing period of your policy. If any payment is rejected for any reason, including insufficient funds, your applicable policy(ies) may be cancelled and you will have no coverage. Late or failed payments will result in a lapse of coverage. Your coverage will be terminated if we have not received payment as of midnight, Mountain Time, of the policy renewal date. The first payment will be billed immediately and you will be auto–debited on the day the coverage period begins; all other payment obligations will be billed 3–15 days prior to the commencement of the next billing period of your policy.\n\nYou understand that if your policy start date is 120 days or more from today’s date, the premium quoted to you here may be subject to change before the policy is instated. You agree that the policy premium rates and other charges required to keep your policy active may increase from time to time, in accordance with the terms of the policy documents provided by the insurance carrier, and you agree to pay the amounts provided to you when payment is due. You further agree that EIA may back-bill you for such increased fees within a reasonable amount of time after the effective date(s) of such increases.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle3">2. Term and Termination.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody3">The term of each insurance policy placed through EIA is either month-to-month (a monthly continuous policy) or annual (yearly continuous policy). These Terms will remain in place perpetually, so long as you continue to have an insurance policy through EIA, or until either party terminates these Terms by providing seven (7) days prior written notice to the other party. If a cancellation notice is not received prior to a new billing cycle, you will not be refunded any amounts already debited from your account. To terminate these Terms, you must send your notice to cancellations@residentinsure.com or mail it to EIA Cancellations, 4205 Chapel Ridge Ln Lehi, UT 84043. If a recurring payment is rejected by your financial institution, we reserve the right to terminate these Terms by providing written notice to you as outlined above.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle4">3. Limitation of Liability.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody4">EIA\'s liability is limited by law and limited to those damages proximately caused by EIA, and EIA shall not be liable for any special, incidental, or consequential damages arising from any breach of these Terms. If EIA\'s error was unintentional and is determined to have resulted from a bona fide error, EIA\'s liability is limited to actual damages. Neither EIA nor its parent company shall be liable for: (a) any error or omission in processing any authorized recurring debit payment; (b) any payment returned for insufficient funds; © any payment failure because your account is restricted; (d) any network or computer failure resulting in your inability to use this website; (e) circumstances beyond EIA\'s reasonable control that prevent your payment from being processed; (f) your failure to submit a payment sufficiently in advance of your payment due date; (g) any refusal of your financial institution or card issuer to honor your payment; (h) your inability to make a payment because EIA has blocked your access to this website in accordance with these Terms; or (i) any act or omission of any financial institution, electronic funds transfer system, operator or third party service provider, or credit card issuer.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle5">4. Recurring Debit Transactions.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody5">EIA is entitled to use and rely upon the information you provide on this website, but is not responsible for any loss results from mistaken or fraudulent information provided by you or someone who purports to be you. Each recurring debit transaction will be processed using the information you provide when you enroll. EIA has no obligation to provide notice to you of a delinquent payment, which will occur if an authorized recurring debit from your account is rejected, and a payment has not been made by the due date. EIA may, at its discretion, initiate a payment or adjustment from an authorized recurring debit entry that was made in error, and choose the system or third party service provider to be used to process the recurring debit payments.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle6">5. Miscellaneous.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody6">EIA functions as an insurance agent, and not as an insurance carrier. Any protections afforded to EIA under these Terms shall also apply to any EIA parent, subsidiary and affiliated entity. No waiver of any terms will be effective unless in writing. You may not transfer your rights or obligations under these Terms. These Terms are governed by the laws of the State of Utah, without regard to the state’s conflict of laws provisions, and by applicable federal laws and regulations. If any term herein is deemed to be invalid or unenforceable, the remaining terms shall remain valid and enforceable as written. These Terms are in addition to any other agreement you have with EIA. Each party shall bear any and all fees and other charges applicable and designated by its own financial institution(s).</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle7">6. Fraud Warning.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody7">It is a crime to knowingly provide false, incomplete, or misleading information to an insurance company for the purpose of defrauding the company. Penalties include imprisonment, fines, and denial of insurance benefits. Your state may have specific warnings against filing false claim information. In case of same-day coverage enrollment, you certify there have been no losses, accidents, or circumstances that might give rise to a claim under this policy within the previous 24 hours, and you agree that any claims incurred prior to the effective date of the policy shall not be covered thereby.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle8">7. Agreement to Deal Electronically.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody8">All of your transactions with EIA may, at our option, be conducted electronically from start to finish. If we decide to proceed non-electronically, those services will still be governed by the remainder of these Terms unless you enter into different terms on a form provided by us. If the law allows you to withdraw this consent or if we are ever required to deal with you non-electronically, we reserve the right to charge or increase fees and you agree to print or make an electronic copy of these Terms and any other contract or disclosure that we are required to provide to you.\n\nBy submitting payment or other information on any step of a transaction within this website, you agree to conduct such transaction by electronic means. By completing any transaction with us through this website, you are agreeing to conduct an electronic transaction and to use and receive communications through electronic means. You agree to enter the requested information electronically via the Internet, and to be notified regarding any transaction electronically through the email address and/or phone number you have provided. You understand that electronically signed documents have the same legal effect as hard copies with ink signatures. You understand that you may refuse to conduct other electronic transactions in the future.\n\nExcept as otherwise provided in these Terms, we will give you any notices regarding this website by posting them on this website. You also authorize EIA to send notices (including notice of subpoenas or other legal process, if any) via electronic mail. You must check the website for notices, and you will be considered to have received a notice when it is posted on the website, or when sent by us via electronic mail, whether or not received by you. You must keep your email address current and any notice sent by us to an email address that you have provided to us will be considered effective notice.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsTitle9">Membership Agreement</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody9">The following is the Membership Agreement of the ResidentSecure program (the “Program”) between you, the person who has enrolled in the Program (“you”, “your”), and Entrata Insurance Agency, LLC (“EIA”, “we”, “us”, “our”). UPON ENROLLMENT, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF MEMBERSHIP. YOU SHOULD READ THIS MEMBERSHIP AGREEMENT CAREFULLY. If you have any questions regarding your Membership, you may contact our customer service center 24 hours a day at the toll-free number listed on your Membership Card.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle10">1. Membership Benefits.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody10">As a Member, you are entitled to access discounts and/or other benefits on various products and services offered by participating vendors through the ResidentSecure website and customer service center ("Benefits"), as described in your Membership Guide or on the ResidentSecure website ("Program Website"). Some Benefits may not be available in your area. Additionally, the discounts available through the Program may not be used in conjunction with any other discount program. PLEASE SEE YOUR MEMBERSHIP MATERIALS AND THE PROGRAM WEBSITE FOR IMPORTANT DETAILS AND LIMITATIONS. All listed or quoted prices are current prices only and are subject to change without notice. We reserve the right to suspend or end the Program or certain aspects thereof, without prior notice, in our sole discretion. We also reserve the right to suspend or end certain aspects of the Program in certain geographic areas, without prior notice, in our sole discretion.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle11">2. Membership Terms.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody11">Your Membership is effective immediately upon your enrollment in the program and shall continue on a month-to-month basis until cancelled as described below. You may cancel your Membership at any time by calling us at the toll-free number listed on your membership card or by writing us at the address indicated below. Unless you notify us that you wish to cancel your membership by following these instructions, or your membership is otherwise cancelled as provided herein, your Membership will continue automatically and you will be billed the then-current membership fee, which will appear on your statement, depending upon how you enrolled.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle12">3. Payment of Membership Fee.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody12">The payment of your membership fee (which, if applicable, includes any trial period fee as well as enrollment or processing fees and shipping and handling charges) is made automatically by a charge to the payment account authorized by you (the "Payment Account") in accordance with the payment terms to which you agreed. In the event that the Program offer to which you agreed includes a trial period, you may cancel your membership at any time during the trial period and not be charged, other than any one time enrollment or processing fees, and shipping and handling charges, in each case depending on the Program offer to which you agreed, as well as money paid for Benefits ordered by you. We reserve the right to terminate your Membership at any time without notification, including in the event that we are unable to bill the membership fee to your specified Payment Account.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle13">4. Promotional Membership Fee.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody13">From time to time, in our sole discretion, we may provide a reduced membership fee, for a promotional period, to first-time or other selected customers. If you are provided with such a promotional reduction in your membership fee ("Promotional Membership Fee"), your Payment Account will be charged the Promotional Membership Fee for the promotional period. You agree that any such reduced price is only valid for the promotional period established by us, and that the regular applicable periodic membership fee will be charged to your Payment Account following the end of the promotional period. Terms of the Promotional Membership Fee, including the duration and amount of the Promotional Membership Fee, may vary from time to time.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle14">5. Continuation of Membership.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody14">Unless you notify us that you wish to cancel your Membership by following the instructions in the paragraph below titled Termination of Membership, your Membership will continue automatically and you will be billed the then-current membership fee which will appear on your Payment Account statement, depending upon how you enrolled. We reserve the right to increase or decrease the membership fee, or add new fees and charges, from time to time. You agree that unless you cancel your membership prior to the effective date of the membership fee increase, you will be charged the new applicable periodic membership fee on each anniversary date after the effective date of such change, and you authorize us to charge the new applicable periodic membership Fee to your Payment Account. You are solely responsible for any and all fees charged to your Payment Account by the credit or debit card issuer, bank, or financial institution, including but not limited to membership, processing, shipping and handling, overdraft, insufficient funds, and over-the-credit-limit fees, in each case to the extent applicable.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle15">6. Electronic Fund Transfer Authorization.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody15">If the Payment Account you have provided is a checking account, you authorize us to create an electronic funds transfer request ("EFT") which will be presented to your bank for payment from your checking account. Your membership term shall be month-to-month; you therefore authorize us to charge your checking account on a monthly basis, and therefore to effect pre-authorized transfers from your checking account. Your request to pay your recurring monthly membership fee with pre-authorized charges to your checking account and your electronic execution of an acknowledgement of your acceptance of this Membership Agreement ("Electronic Signature") constitutes your pre-authorized EFT authorization for future charges on your checking account and your consent to these terms and conditions. You further acknowledge that the amount charged to your checking account may be different from time to time, in accordance with this Membership Agreement, including, without limitation, differing amounts due to Promotional Membership Fees or changes to your membership plan, and you authorize us to charge your checking account for such varying amounts. You agree that if an EFT is returned unpaid, you will pay a service charge up to the maximum amount allowed by law. EFTs returned for insufficient or uncollected funds, together with service charges, may be debited electronically from your account or collected using a bank draft drawn from your account. You may cancel your membership as described in these Terms. Such cancellation will cancel any checking account authorization that was to occur on any day after the date of cancellation. You may also cancel your pre-authorized debit authorization by contacting your bank within a sufficient time to cancel the authorization (Please see your agreement with your bank for the terms and conditions of cancellation). Please note, however, that you must still notify us of the cancellation of your membership as described herein, as cancellation of your authorization with your bank will not serve as notice to us concerning cancellation of your membership.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle16">7. Use of Membership.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody16">Your Membership is non-assignable and non-transferable. You agree that only you—or if the Family Plan is selected, you, your spouse, your domestic partner, and your children up to and including age 25 who are residing at your address or attending school—may use the Membership. Benefits are not to be resold. You are limited to one membership per twelve-month period per immediate family. You are responsible for all use of your Membership and will promptly notify us if you become aware of any unauthorized use of your Membership, your membership card or membership number, or if your membership card is lost or stolen. If you were offered the opportunity to claim a premium or gift in connection with your enrollment in the Program, you are limited to one premium or gift per Program and, depending upon the offer you agreed to, you may be required to be a member of the Program at the time that your claim is processed.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle17">8. Disclaimer of Liability.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody17">You agree that EIA and our subsidiaries, affiliates, partners and providers are not responsible or liable for any Benefits provided by participating vendors and, if you have any claims relating to such Benefits, you will make your claim against the vendors providing the Benefit. WE MAKE NO WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING THE WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WITH RESPECT TO ANY OF THE BENEFITS OR RELATED INFORMATION PROVIDED TO YOU. We do not guarantee, nor are responsible for, the quality of products or services provided by any independent vendors.\n\nWe reserve the right to eliminate, add, change and substitute Benefits and participating vendors without notice to you in our sole discretion. We assume no responsibility for the payment of or contribution to any use or sales tax on the Benefits which may be imposed by taxing authorities, and such taxes, to the extent imposed, shall remain your sole responsibility or that of the provider of the Benefits, as the case may be.\n\nIN NO EVENT SHALL WE OR ANY OF OUR AFFILIATES, PARTNERS OR PROVIDERS, OR ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OR OTHER REPRESENTATIVES, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE, OR AGGRAVATED DAMAGES, OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROGRAM, PROGRAM WEBSITE, MEMBERSHIP GUIDE, ANY MATERIALS, INFORMATION, QUALIFICATIONS AND RECOMMENDATIONS APPEARING ON ANY PROGRAM WEBSITE, ANY SOFTWARE, TOOLS, TIPS, PRODUCTS, OR SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH, CONTAINED IN, OR ADVERTISED ON ANY PROGRAM WEBSITE, AND/OR ANY LINK PROVIDED ON ANY PROGRAM WEBSITE, WHETHER OR NOT WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. THIS PROVISION SHALL SURVIVE THE TERMINATION OF YOUR MEMBERSHIP.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle18">9. Changes to Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody18">We may, at any time, and at our sole discretion, modify this Membership Agreement by posting the modified Membership Agreement on the Program Website. You agree to review this Membership Agreement periodically on the Program Website. If you do not agree to any modification of this Membership Agreement, you must immediately cancel your membership. Continuing your membership following any such modifications will constitute your acceptance of the modified Membership Agreement.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle19">10. Termination of Membership.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody19">YOU MAY TERMINATE THIS MEMBERSHIP AGREEMENT AND YOUR MEMBERSHIP AT ANY TIME BY CALLING US AT THE TOLL-FREE NUMBER LISTED ON YOUR MEMBERSHIP CARD/MATERIALS OR BY NOTIFYING US IN WRITING AT CUSTOMER SERVICE, Entrata Insurance Agency, 4205 Chapel Ridge Rd., LEHI, UT 84043. YOUR CANCELLATION WILL BE PROCESSED PROMPTLY UPON THE RECEIPT OF YOUR CANCELLATION REQUEST. UPON CANCELLATION, YOU WILL NOT OWE ANY FURTHER MEMBERSHIP FEES AND WILL NOT BE ENTITLED TO A REFUND OF PAST FEES CHARGED TO YOUR ACCOUNT. DEPENDING UPON THE TERMS YOU AGREED TO, ANY ENROLLMENT, PROCESSING AND/OR TRIAL PERIOD FEES MAY NOT BE REFUNDABLE. ANY OTHER FEES OR CHARGES INCURRED IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROGRAM (INCLUDING BANK OR OVERDRAFT CHARGES) ARE YOUR RESPONSIBILITY. WE WILL TERMINATE YOUR MEMBERSHIP IF IT IS NOT USED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS MEMBERSHIP AGREEMENT OR YOU HAVE NOT PROPERLY ENROLLED IN THE PROGRAM. IN SUCH A CASE, WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO: (1) NOT REFUND MEMBERSHIP FEES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY ENROLLMENT OR PROCESSING FEES, SHIPPING AND HANDLING CHARGES AND OTHER FEES, IN EACH CASE TO THE EXTENT APPLICABLE) PAID BY YOU AND/OR (2) NOT FULFILL ANY PENDING ORDERS FOR BENEFITS PURCHASED PRIOR TO CANCELLATION OF THE MEMBERSHIP. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO TERMINATE YOUR MEMBERSHIP AT ANY TIME FOR ANY OTHER REASON. MEMBERs are PROHIBITED FROM RE-ENROLLING IN THE PROGRAM FOR TWELVE (12) MONTHS FOLLOWING CANCELLATION.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle20">11. Entire Agreement.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody20">These Terms, along with any terms that you agreed to while accessing the EIA website, contains all of the terms and conditions of Membership, and no representations, inducements, promises, or agreements concerning the Membership not included in these Terms shall be effective or enforceable. If any of the provisions of these Terms shall become invalid or unenforceable, the remaining terms shall remain in full force and effect as written.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle21">12. Governing Law.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody21">THIS MEMBERSHIP AGREEMENT AND THE TERMS OF MEMBERSHIP SHALL BE GOVERNED AND CONSTRUED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS OF THE STATE OF UTAH, WITHOUT GIVING EFFECT TO THE CHOICE OF LAW PROVISIONS THEREOF.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle22">13. Arbitration.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody22">PLEASE READ THIS PROVISION CAREFULLY. IT PROVIDES THAT ANY DISPUTE MAY BE RESOLVED BY BINDING ARBITRATION. ARBITRATION REPLACES THE RIGHT TO GO TO COURT, INCLUDING THE RIGHT TO BRING OR PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION OR SIMILAR PROCEEDING. IN ARBITRATION, A DISPUTE IS RESOLVED BY AN ARBITRATOR INSTEAD OF A JUDGE OR JURY. THE ARBITRATOR\'S DECISION WILL GENERALLY BE FINAL AND BINDING. ARBITRATION PROCEDURES ARE SIMPLER AND MORE LIMITED THAN COURT PROCEDURES.\n\nAny claim, dispute or controversy between you and us (or made by or against anyone connected with you or us, or claiming through you or us) arising from or relating to your membership ("Claim"), including Claims regarding applicability or validity of this arbitration provision, shall be resolved by binding arbitration in accordance with the rules of the American Arbitration Association ("AAA") (except for any AAA rules providing for class claims or class arbitration) then in effect, subject to this Membership Agreement.\n\nAny Claim regarding the validity or enforceability of this arbitration provision shall be governed by the laws of the State of Utah, without giving effect to the choice of law provisions thereof. This arbitration provision is made pursuant to a transaction involving interstate commerce and, in all other respects, including the determination of any questions about whether Claims are within the scope of this arbitration provision and therefore subject to arbitration shall be governed by the Federal Arbitration Act, 9 U.S.C. §1–16 ("FAA"), and shall be resolved by interpreting the arbitration provision in the broadest way the law will allow it to be construed.\n\nAll Claims are subject to arbitration, no matter what theory they are based on or what remedy they seek. This includes Claims based on contract, tort (including intentional tort), fraud, agency, negligence, statutory or regulatory provisions, or any other source of law. Claims made and remedies sought as part of a class action, private attorney general or other representative action are subject to arbitration on an individual (non-class, non-representative) basis. As an exception to arbitration, you and EIA retain the right to pursue in a small claims court located in the federal judicial district that includes your billing address at the time of the Claim, any Claim that is within the court\'s jurisdiction and proceeds on an individual basis.\n\nThe arbitration shall be conducted before a single arbitrator, applying to the Claims the substantive laws of the State of Utah without giving effect to the choice of law provisions thereof. The arbitrator\'s authority is limited solely to the Claims between you and us alone. The arbitration will not be consolidated with any other arbitration proceeding. You and EIA do not agree to any arbitration on a class action or representative basis, and the arbitrator shall not be authorized to treat any Claim on a class action or representative basis. If you prevail in the arbitration of any Claim against us, we will reimburse you for any fees that you paid to the AAA in connection with the arbitration. Any decision rendered will be final and binding on the parties, and judgment may be entered in a court of competent jurisdiction. Arbitration rules and forms may be obtained from the AAA at http://www.adr.org/. Claims shall be filed in any AAA office. However, any participatory hearing that you attend shall take place in Salt Lake City, Utah, unless you chose to have the hearing take place in the federal judicial district that includes your billing address at the time the arbitration Claim is filed.\n\nThis arbitration provision applies to all Claims now in existence or that may arise in the future. The arbitration provision shall survive termination of your membership as well as voluntary payment of the debt in full by you or any bankruptcy by you.\n\nIF YOU DO NOT CHOOSE TO ACCEPT THIS BINDING ARBITRATION PROVISION, YOU MUST NOTIFY US IN WRITING, WITHIN TWENTY (20) DAYS AFTER RECEIPT OF THIS MEMBERSHIP AGREEMENT, BY REGISTERED MAIL AT ARBITRATION OPT-OUT, ENTRATA INSURANCE AGENCY, 4205 CHAPEL RIDGE RD., LEHI, UT 84043. IF YOU SO NOTIFY US BY THAT TIME THAT YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THE BINDING ARBITRATION PROVISION, YOU MAY CONTINUE TO BE A MEMBER FOR THE CURRENT MEMBERSHIP TERM UNLESS THE MEMBERSHIP IS OTHERWISE TERMINATED HEREUNDER. HOWEVER, IN THE EVENT YOUR MEMBERSHIP IS CONTINUED, WE SHALL HAVE THE RIGHT NOT TO RENEW YOUR MEMBERSHIP AT THE END OF THE FIRST ANNIVERSARY OF YOUR ENROLLMENT DATE.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle23">14. Availability Restrictions.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody23">This program is only available to residents of the contiguous United States (excluding any such states as we may designate from time to time in your Membership Guide and/or the Program Website). Orders to U.S. military post offices cannot be fulfilled.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsSubtitle24">15. Consent to Electronic Communications.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsBody24">You consent to receive communications from us about your membership electronically, either by e-mail or by notices posted on the Program Website, as determined by us in our sole discretion. You agree that any requirement that a notice, disclosure, agreement, or other communication be sent to you by us in writing is satisfied by such electronic communication. You agree that we may send you e-mails which include notices about your membership as well as information pertaining to the Program and services, such as featured products/services or new offerings. You agree that this information is part of your membership with us.</string>


    <!-- Terms of use -->
    <string name="termsOfUseTitle1">Use of Site</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody1">Entrata Insurance Agency dba ResidentInsureTM ("EIA") provides the "User" access to the Website subject to these Terms and Conditions of Use. By accessing or using this website, including information made available on this site (collectively, the "site"), and/or availing yourself of the services offered herein (collectively the "services") user accepts these terms and conditions, including all terms, policies, and guidelines incorporated by reference (collectively, the "terms") and any modifications that may be made to the terms from time to time. If user does not agree to any provision of the terms, he / she may not access or use the site.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle2">1. Modifications to Terms.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody2">EIA reserves the right to change or modify any of the terms and conditions contained herein, and any other terms, policies, or guidelines, at any time and in its sole discretion. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting of the revisions on the Site. User\'s continued use of the Site following the posting of such changes or modifications will constitute acceptance of such changes or modifications.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle3">2. Copyrights and Limited Trademarks.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody3">The Site and all content and materials available on the Site, including, without limitation, any logos, designs, text, documents, graphics, software, videos, sound files, and the selection and arrangement thereof (collectively, "Content"), are the proprietary property of EIA and are protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The EIA names and logos, and any other product or service name or slogan contained on the Site and in any Content are trademarks of EIA and may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of EIA or the applicable trademark holder. Except for those rights expressly granted in these Terms, no other rights are granted, either express or implied under these Terms. Unless stated explicitly in these Terms, nothing in these Terms will be construed as conferring any license to intellectual property rights, whether by estoppel, implication or otherwise.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle4">3. No Spam Policy.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody4">User acknowledges and agrees that any unauthorized use of the Site or EIA"s computer systems (e.g., unsolicited email advertisements) is a violation of these terms and certain federal and state laws, including without limitation the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act (18 U.S.C. § 1030 et seq.). Such violations may subject the User or its agents to civil and criminal penalties.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle5">4. Dealings with Site Users.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody5">Any fees or payments collected by EIA applicable to transactions set forth on the Site, and all terms and conditions applicable to such fees or payments are set forth in the Site\'s Terms of Sale (defined in Section 7 below). THE SITE IS PROVIDED AS-IS AND USE OF THE SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY PURCHASE, SALE, LEASE, OR OTHER TRANSACTIONS BY OR WITH SITE USERS OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES THAT RELATE TO THE SITE, ARE AT USERS OWN RISK.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle6">5. Taxes.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody6">User is responsible for determining whether sales, use, and other taxes apply to any transaction or other dealings relating to the use of the Site. Users must collect, report, and remit the correct tax to the appropriate tax authority. EIA is not obligated to determine whether sales, use, or similar taxes apply to any transactions or other dealings relating in any manner to the Site, and, except as stated expressly on the Site, is not responsible for collecting, reporting, or remitting any sales, use, or similar taxes arising from any transactions or dealings relating to the Site.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle7">6. Registration Data Account Security.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody7">In consideration of the use of the Site, User agrees to (a) provide accurate, current and complete information about User as may be prompted by registration forms on the Site ("Registration Data") (b) maintain the security of any logins, passwords, or other credentials that User selects or that are provided for use on the Site and (c) maintain and promptly update the Registration Data, and any other information User provides to EIA, and to keep all such information accurate, current, and complete.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle8">7. Paid Services.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody8">EIA offers Services on the Site that require the payment of fees. Services, are made available subject to additional terms and conditions ("Terms of Sale") that supplement these Terms which are made available and must be agreed to in connection with the purchase of any Services by User. Cancellations and modifications will be processed by EIA in a timely manner. EIA will not refund any pre-paid fees paid for Services during the month in which a cancellation or modification request was received. EIA makes no guarantees with respect to the results expected or realized by Customer through the Services.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle9">8. Indemnification.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody9">User will defend, indemnify and hold harmless EIA, its parents, subsidiaries and affiliates, and their respective directors, officers, agents, employees, licensors, and suppliers from and against any costs, damages, expenses, and liabilities (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys\' fees) arising out of or related to its use of the Site, violation of these Terms, or violation of any rights of a third party.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle10">9. Disclaimer of Warranties.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody10">USER AGREES THAT USE OF THE SITE AND THE SERVICES IS ENTIRELY AT USER"S OWN RISK. THE SITE AND THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS” OR "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. ALL EXPRESS AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF PROPRIETARY RIGHTS ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED. EIA DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES FOR THE SECURITY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, ACCURACY, AND PERFORMANCE OF THE SITE AND FOR THE RESULTS OF THE SERVICES. EIA DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES FOR OTHER SERVICES OR GOODS RECEIVED THROUGH OR ADVERTISED ON THE SITE OR SERVICES, OR ACCESSED THROUGH ANY LINKS ON THE SITE. EIA DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES FOR VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE OR THE SERVICES.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle11">10. Limitation of Liability.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody11">NEITHER EIA NOR ITS PARENT, SUPPLIERS OR LICENSORS WILL BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA, OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF EIA OR ANY SUPPLIER OR LICENSOR HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF THESE DAMAGES), ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO USER"S ACCESS TO OR USE OF, OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE, THE SITE, ANY CONTENT OR SERVICES. NEITHER EIA NOR ITS PARENT COMPANY SHALL BE HELD LIABLE FOR: A RESULT OF AN ERROR OR OMISSION IN PROCESSING ANY AUTHORIZED RECURRING DEBIT PAYMENT OR, YOU DO NOT HAVE ENOUGH MONEY IN YOUR ACCOUNT TO MAKE YOUR PAYMENT OR, A TRANSFER OF MONEY FROM YOUR ACCOUNT IS RESTRICTED OR, THIS WEBSITE WAS NOT WORKING OR, CIRCUMSTANCES BEYOND EIA"S CONTROL PREVENT PAYMENT DESPITE REASONABLE PRECAUTIONS OR, YOU FAIL TO USE THIS WEBSITE PROPERLY OR FAIL TO PROPERLY SECURE YOUR COMPUTER FROM VIRUSES, SPYWARE, TROJAN HORSES, OR OTHER MALICIOUS CODE OR, YOU DO NOT REQUEST PAYMENT SUFFICIENTLY IN ADVANCE OF YOUR PAYMENT DUE DATE OR, YOUR FINANCIAL INSTITUTION OR CARD ISSUER REFUSES TO HONOR YOUR PAYMENT OR, EIA HAS BLOCKED YOUR ACCESS TO THIS WEBSITE OR, THIS WEBSITE HAS BEEN TERMINATED OR SUSPENDED OR, THIS WEBSITE INDICATES YOUR REQUEST WILL NOT BE PROCESSED OR, FROM ANY ACT OR OMISSION OF ANY FINANCIAL INSTITUTION, ELECTRONIC FUNDS TRANSFER SYSTEM, OPERATOR OR THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDER, OR CREDIT CARD ISSUER. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY. THE MAXIMUM TOTAL LIABILITY OF EIA AND ITS SUPPLIERS AND LICENSORS FOR ALL CLAIMS UNDER THESE TERMS, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, OR OTHERWISE, IS THE AMOUNT ACTUALLY PAID, BY USER TO EIA FOR USE OF THE SITE AND THE SERVICES IN THE TWELVE MONTHS PRECEDING THE APPLICABLE CLAIM. EACH PROVISION OF THESE TERMS THAT PROVIDES FOR A LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES, OR EXCLUSION OF DAMAGES IS TO ALLOCATE THE RISKS UNDER THESE TERMS BETWEEN THE PARTIES. THIS ALLOCATION IS AN ESSENTIAL ELEMENT OF THE BASIS OF THE BARGAIN BETWEEN THE PARTIES. EACH OF THESE PROVISIONS IS SEVERABLE AND INDEPENDENT OF ALL OTHER PROVISIONS OF THESE TERMS. THE LIMITATIONS IN THIS SECTION WILL APPLY EVEN IF ANY LIMITED REMEDY FAILS OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle12">11. Restrictions on Access Downtime.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody12">Access to and use of the Site and Services may be temporarily down, inaccessible, or deactivated due to maintenance, upgrades, equipment failure, power failure, and/or other scheduled or unscheduled downtimes or interruptions and EIA shall not be liable to User or any third party for any such circumstances. Neither EIA nor its suppliers or licensors will be liable to User or to any third party for any modification, discontinuance, or restriction of the Site or Services.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle13">12. Consent to Electronic Communications.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody13">By using the Site, User consents to receiving electronic communications from EIA. These communications may include notices about User’s account and information concerning or related to the Site. User agrees that any notices, agreements, disclosures, or other communications that EIA sends electronically will satisfy any legal communication requirements, including that such communications be in writing.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle14">13. General Legal Notices.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody14">EIA’s failure to act in a particular circumstance does not waive its ability to act with respect to that circumstance or similar circumstances. Any provision of these Terms that is found to be invalid, unlawful, or unenforceable will be severed from these Terms, and the remaining provisions of these Terms will continue to be in full force and effect. The section headings and titles in these Terms are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect. Any provision in these Terms that by its nature should survive the termination of User’s license to access the Site or any termination of these Terms (including, without limitation, provisions governing indemnification, limitations on liability, disclaimers of warranty, and ownership of intellectual property) will continue to remain in full force and effect after any such termination. These Terms are governed by the laws of the State of Utah, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to the Site, Services or these Terms must be commenced within one year after the claim arose and will be settled by binding arbitration in accordance with the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association. Any such controversy or claim will be arbitrated on an individual basis, and will not be consolidated in any arbitration with any claim or controversy of any other party. The arbitration will be conducted in Salt Lake City, Utah, and judgment on the arbitration award may be entered into any court of competent jurisdiction. The award of the arbitrator will be final and binding upon the parties without appeal or review except as permitted by Utah law. Either party may seek any interim or preliminary injunctive relief from any court of competent jurisdiction, as necessary to protect the party"s rights or property pending the completion of arbitration. These Terms, including all policies and guidelines incorporated into these Terms by reference, constitute the entire agreement between User and EIA concerning the Site and Services. These Terms supersede all prior agreements or communications between User and EIA regarding the subject matter of these Terms.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle15">14. Underwriting Entities.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody15">You are provided the following information pursuant to various state insurance laws, including, but not limited to those of CA, MA and MO.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle16">Company Name:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody16">Markel American Insurance Company</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle17">NAIC #</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody17">785–28932</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle18">Address:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody18">P.O. Box 906, Pewaukee, WI 53072–0906</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle19">Phone:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody19">(262)–548–9880</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle20">State of Domicile:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody20">VA</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody21">Authorized to do business in all 50 states and the District of Columbia</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle22">Company Name:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody22">Unitrin Direct Property &amp; Casualty Company</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle23">NAIC #</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody23">10915</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle24">Address:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody24">One East Wacker Drive, Chicago, IL 60601</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle25">Phone:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody25">(800)–637–2782</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle26">State of Domicile:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody26">Illinois</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody27">Authorized to do business in 46 states and the District of Columbia</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle28">Company Name:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody28">Praetorian Insurance Company (QBE)</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle29">NAIC #</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody29">37257</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle30">Address:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody30">Wall Street Plaza, 88 Pine Street, NY 10005</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle31">Phone:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody31">(877)–577–0850</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle32">State of Domicile:</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody32">California</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody33">Product and coverage options are subject to availability by state. See the actual policy for terms, conditions, limitations and/or exclusions that may apply.</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseSubtitle34">15. Questions &amp; Contact Information</string>
    <string name="termsOfUseBody34">User should direct any questions or comments about the Site to EIA at service@residentinsure.com.\n\nThese Terms and Conditions may vary by state. All statements are subject to the terms and conditions of the applicable policy.</string>


    <!-- FAQs -->
    <string name="fAQsTitle1">FAQs</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle1">How do I file a claim?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody1">To file a claim call whichever of the following numbers your policy number corresponds with\n1. For policies that start with RTH call Markel American Insurance at 1–800–236–3113\n2. For policies that start with PRH call QBE at 1–844–723–2524\n3. For ID theft policies (Only numbers and 12 digits long) please call 1–866–434–3572</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle2">How do I set up a Policy?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody2">You can set up a policy by either calling 1–877–577–0850 or clicking on “Get a Quote” on our website</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle3">How to make changes to a policy?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody3">A policyholder can either log into residentinsure.com to make most changes or call our agency team at 1–877–577–0850. Some changes, like address changes, can only be done via phone.</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle4">Who can make changes to my account?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody4">Only people listed on the policy can make changes to the policy. If you are paying for someone else’s policy, it is generally recommended you have yourself added to the policy so you can make changes.</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle5">Why am I not getting a password reset link?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody5">There are a few reasons why someone may not receive their reset password link right away:\n1. The most common reason is that the capitalization is not correct. Our system is case sensitive and if the email address you request the password with does not match exactly what is saved with the account it will not send.\n2. Reset password links typically only take a few seconds to send, however they can occasionally take up to 30 minutes before you receive them.\n3. Another reason can be the policyholder used a different email address</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle6">How to contact our agency team?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody6">You can call 1–877–577–0850 Monday through Friday from 8AM EST to 8PM EST. We are closed for major holidays.</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle7">How do I find my policy number?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody7">All billing notification emails will contain the policy number, we also include it on the proof of insurance, policy packet, and on the website once you have logged in.</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle8">How is communication sent?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody8">All communication between the policyholder and ResidentInsure will be sent via email. If you do not have an email address it is not recommended to purchase a policy through ResidentInsure.</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle9">When does my policy end?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody9">All of our policies are continuous until they are either canceled by the policyholder or we are no longer able to process payments and the policy lapses.</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle10">When does billing happen?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody10">Billing is based on the start date and will bill 3–15 days before the start date depending on the type of policy and carrier. Occasionally we will need to perform a mid-billing cycle catch-up payment that will not fall between these dates. The only way to change the billing date is to cancel the policy and change the start date.</string>
    <string name="fAQsSubtitle11">When do I receive my policy?</string>
    <string name="fAQsBody11">The proof of insurance/declaration page is available after the first payment has been processed which typically takes 24 hours. The full policy packet will be sent 2 weeks after the policy start date.</string>


    <!-- Privacy Notice -->
    <string name="privacyNoticeTitle1">Privacy Notice</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody1">Effective Date: 04–01–2023\n\nEntrata Insurance Agency, LLC. (collectively, "ResidentInsure", "we", "us", "our") are committed to protecting individual privacy and maintaining the trust of our customers who purchase a policy or other services through us ("Customers"), business clients of us or our parent company, Entrata, Inc. (“Clients”), and visitors to our websites (collectively, "Visitors"). It is important to us that we provide transparency regarding our collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information (for purposes of this Privacy Notice, we use the California Consumer Privacy Act’s (“CCPA”) definition of “Personal Information”).\n\nTo help us meet this commitment to you, we have created this Privacy Notice ("Privacy Notice"). This Privacy Notice governs data protection matters across our suite of products and services (collectively, the "ResidentInsure Platforms" or "Platforms"), including data provided by Visitors to the websites we control and that link to this Privacy Notice ("ResidentInsure Site"). This Privacy Notice, along with our Terms of Use, form an integral and binding part of our relationship with you.\n\nPlease Note: This Privacy Notice does not contemplate any processing of Personal Information covered by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle2">1. WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY NOTICE APPLY TO?</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody2">This Privacy Notice describes how we use, share, and protect the Personal Information of Customers and Visitors who visit the ResidentInsure Site. It also describes the rights and choices regarding use, access to, and correction of Personal Information available.\n\nImportant to Note:\n\nResidentInsure provides its Platforms for use by our Clients, which are typically residential and commercial real estate property managers and property owners. Our Clients use our Platforms to manage the administration of renter’s insurance to its tenants. Any use of Client Data by us is carried out pursuant to an agreement (and/or our applicable Terms of Service) in place between ResidentInsure and our Client.\n\nIf you, as a Customer or Visitor, have any questions or concerns about the data handling practices of an ResidentInsure Client using our Platforms to process and store your personal information, please contact the relevant Client directly.\n\nFinally, Our ResidentInsure Site may contain links to other third-party websites. The information practices and content of such third-party websites are governed by their own privacy notices. We encourage you to review the privacy notices of such third-party websites to understand their information practices.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle3">2. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND WHY?</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody3">We may collect Personal Information in various ways, including in connection with your application for a quote, to process and manage your insurance policy, offer you additional products and services that we think may be of interest to you, for analytics purposes, and when you contact our customer services; or in connection with your inquiries and communications with us. We may also collect Personal Information from other sources, including Clients and data companies.\n\nWe have created the following table to help you understand the categories of Personal Information that we are responsible for, and process:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle4">Categories of Personal Information:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle5">Customer Information:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle6">Specific Types of Personal Information:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody6">Contact Information: First and last name, email address, phone number, residence information.\n\nInsurance Details: Insured unit number, lease period, co-occupants (co-residents, co-tenants), bank account, credit/debit card\n\nOperational Data: Transactions, policy coverage levels, account balances, billing information, sales, purchases, uses, supplier information, credentials to online services and platforms, and electronic content produced by individuals using company systems, including online interactive and voice communications such as through email, phone or, network sessions.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle7">Source:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody7">Directly from our Clients and from you.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle8">Why We Collect It – Our Purposes</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody8">Communicate with Customers for the purpose of supporting our contractual relationship. This includes: \n\n\u2022 Informing Customers about our various insurance products and services, and providing access to our Platforms where the Customer sets up an account with us.\n\u2022 Tracking and responding to Customer’ inquiries, reviews or correspondence regarding products and services.\n\u2022 Administering Customer account(s).\n\u2022 Providing and improving our customer service.\n\u2022 Facilitating communications generally in the context of our business activities.\n\u2022 Sending administrative information to Customers, such as changes to our terms, conditions and policies.\n\u2022 Enforcing our Terms of Use and any other contractual terms and conditions that govern the relationship between ResidentInsureand our Customers.\n\u2022 Continuously improving, customizing and personalizing our Platforms.\n\u2022 Analyzing and improving the safety and security of our Platforms.\n\u2022 Connecting with vendors via APIs to allow vendors to provide specific services directly to Clients.\n\u2022 Carrying out machine learning, data extracting and loading data in data warehouses, in order to support ResidentInsure enterprise software, data access, modifications, operations, and provide access to third parties via secure integrations.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle9">Prospective Customer Data:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle10">Specific Types of Personal Information:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody10">First and last name, email address, employer, phone number, residence information.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle11">Source:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody11">Directly from Prospective Customer.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle12">Why We Collect It – Our Purposes</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody12">Contact prospective Customers. This includes:\n\n\u2022 For marketing purposes, such as re-engaging with prospective Customers who have expressed an interest in our Platforms.\n\u2022 Administering account access to our Platforms.\n\u2022 Responding to inquiries, for example, when you send us questions, suggestions, compliments or complaints, or when you request further information about our services</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle13">Prospective Client Personnel Data:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle14">Specific Types of Personal Information:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody14">First and last name, email address, employer, phone number (work), physical address (work), job title.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle15">Source:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody15">Directly from Prospective Client Personnel.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle16">Why We Collect It – Our Purposes</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody16">Contact prospective Clients in order to set up demos of our Platforms. This includes:\n\n\u2022 For marketing purposes, such as re-engaging with prospective Clients who have expressed an interest in our Platforms.\n\u2022 Administering account access to our Platforms.\n\u2022 Responding to inquiries, for example, when you send us questions, suggestions, compliments or complaints, or when you request further information about our services</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle17">Visitors:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle18">Specific Types of Personal Information:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody18">Contact Information: Name, company, business address, business email, business telephone.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle19">Source:</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody19">Directly from Visitors to our Site.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle20">Why We Collect It – Our Purposes</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody20">Provide you with our newsletter and/or other marketing materials and facilitate social sharing with your consent or where we have a legitimate interest. This includes:\n\n\u2022 Sending you marketing related emails, with information about our services, new products and other news about our company.\n\u2022 Facilitating social sharing functionality that you choose to use.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle21">3. HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody21">We do not use Personal Information for purposes that are materially different to the purposes for which they were originally collected, as set out in Section 2. If these purposes change in the future, we will provide you with notice and a request to consent to (or an opportunity to opt-out of) this new use where so required by applicable law.\n\n“Do Not Track” Notice: “Do Not Track” is a preference that you can set in your browser to let websites you visit know that you do not want them collecting certain information about you. ResidentInsure does not currently respond to, or honor, Do Not Track signals or requests from your browser.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle22">4. HOW DO WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL DATA?</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody22">We will not disclose any personal information that we collect from you to any external parties except as indicated below (for CCPA purposes, all of the below categories of data recipients are classified as Service Providers or Third Parties, as those terms are defined):\n\n\u2022 Our Affiliates. Entrata Insurance Agency, LLC is a wholly owned subsidiary of Entrata, Inc. We may disclose personal information to our parent company Entrata, Inc. and any subsidiaries and affiliates within the Entrata corporate group (click here for a list of Entrata\'s subsidiaries).\n\u2022 Service Providers. We may disclose personal information to our service providers who perform certain services necessary to run our business (for example, insurance companies, insurance agents, underwriters, data hosting and development, data analysis, customer service, auditing and other services), provided that these service providers have entered into legally binding agreements with us to protect the personal information shared, limit their use, retention, and disclosure of the personal information, and assist us with our compliance requirements.\n\u2022 Legal Request. We may disclose personal information to comply with applicable law and our regulatory monitoring and reporting obligations (which may include laws outside your country of residence), to respond to requests from public and government authorities (which may include authorities outside your country of residence), to cooperate with law enforcement, or for other legal reasons.\n\u2022 Business Transfer. We may disclose personal information to a buyer or successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of ResidentInsure\’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, receivership, or similar proceeding in which personal information held by Entrata are among the assets to be transferred.\n\u2022 Enforcement of Our or Others\' Rights. We may disclose personal information to external parties the extent that this is necessary to enforce or protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you, or others, including enforcing our Terms of Use and any other agreements (such as for billing and collection purposes and fraud prevention).</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle23">5. CHILDREN.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody23">We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of seventeen (17) without authorization by a holder of parental responsibility. If you believe that we may have collected personal information from or about a child under the age of seventeen (17), please send an email to dataprivacy@residentinsure.com with the subject line "Personal Data of a Minor.”</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle24">6. HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody24">We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a username and password (either as a Client or an End User) to access our Platforms, you are responsible for keeping this information confidential and preventing unauthorized access to your account. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us in accordance with the "How to Contact Us" section below.\n\nWhere we collect your payment card information, we will comply with all applicable Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS).</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle25">7. RETAINING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody25">We retain personal information for as long as needed or permitted in light of the purpose(s) for which they were obtained and consistent with applicable law. The criteria used to determine our retention periods include:\n\n\u2022 The length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you or our Client, and provide the use of our Platforms to you or our Client (for example, for as long as you have an account with us or keep using the Platforms);\n\u2022 Whether there is a legal obligation to which we are subject (for example, certain laws require us to keep records of your transactions for a certain period of time before we can delete them); or\n\u2022 Whether retention is advisable in light of our legal position (such as in regard to applicable statutes of limitations, litigation or regulatory investigations).</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle26">8. KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION UPDATED.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody26">Where you have set up an account on one of our Platforms through our Clients, it is up to you to keep your personal information up to date. If you are unable to update your personal information, please contact our relevant Client with which you have a primary relationship. If our Client is unable to assist you, we will endeavor to assist our Client with updating your information.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle27">9. INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA CONSUMERS.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody27">The information and rights in this section apply specifically to California residents.\n\nIn compliance with the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), ResidentInsure does not sell, trade, or rent any Personal Information, nor have we done so in the preceding twelve months.\n\nResidentInsure has not sold the Personal Information of minors under 16 years of age without first attaining affirmative authorization.\n\nCalifornia residents are entitled to contact us to request information about whether we have disclosed Personal Information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.Currently ResidentInsure does not disclose Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Thus, upon receipt of such a request by a California consumer, and as required by California state law, we will respond with either (1) a confirmation that we have not disclosed any Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the previous calendar year, or (2) if our practices have changed, provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, whichever is relevant. California consumers may request further information about our compliance with this law by emailing us at dataprivacy@residentinsure.com.\n\nUnder the CCPA, California consumers have various rights regarding the Personal Information that we collect and process using ResidentInsure’s platforms.\n\nNote: These rights are only exercisable directly against ResidentInsure when we are determining the purposes and means of processing of your Personal Information (which we generally do if you are a Customer, prospective Customer, an employee of one of our Clients or someone we are sending marketing communications to). Please reach out to our Clients if you, as a Customer or Visitor, have any questions or concerns about the data handling practices of an ResidentInsure Client using our Platforms to process and store your personal information.\n\nCalifornia consumers have the right to:\n\n\u2022 Request disclosure of the categories and specific pieces of Personal Information that a Business has collected about you;\n\u2022 Request disclosure of the categories of third–party sources, if any, from which a Business has collected Personal Information about you;\n\u2022 Disclosure of the Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which your Personal Information has been collected;\n\u2022 Receive a list of the categories of third parties with whom a business has shared your Personal Information;\n\u2022 Request that a business delete any Personal Information that it has collected from you (subject to exceptions).\n\u2022 Not be discriminated against by a business (e.g. charged different rates, provided different levels of service, denied goods or services, or suggested any of the preceding) for exercising any of the individual rights granted above.\n\u2022 Designate an authorized agent to exercise any of the individual rights granted above, on your behalf.\n\u2022 Opt–out of the sale of Personal Information, if applicable.\n\nTo exercise any of your rights as a California consumer, you should contact ResidentInsure by sending an email to dataprivacy@residentinsure.com or filling out this form or by calling (866) 249–1066.\n\nBefore complying with your request, we may need to verify that it is you that is making the request. To accomplish this, you (or your authorized agent) may be requested to (1) confirm specific pieces of Personal Information that we already know about you, or (2) provide us with appropriate identification depending on the sensitivity of the information requested. California consumers are limited to two requests for Personal Information per twelve-month period.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle28">10. CUSTOMER PAYMENT INFORMATION.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody28">Your payment information may be processed via third party payment processors in accordance with such payment processors’ terms and policies. We transmit your complete payment information when you initiate a payment through the ResidentInsure Platform. We temporarily collect this information only so that we can pass it along to our payment processors, which you agree to use by submitting a payment through the ResidentInsurePlatform. We do not store your payment information.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle29">11. UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody29">It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Notice on this page, with a notice that it has been updated on our main homepage. If we make material changes to how we treat your Personal Information, we will notify you through a notice on the homepage. The date that this Privacy Notice was last revised is listed at the top of the page. You are responsible for visiting our site and this Privacy Notice to check for any changes.</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeSubtitle30">12. HOW TO CONTACT US?</string>
    <string name="privacyNoticeBody30">If you have any questions or complaints related to our practices with respect to the collection, use, or disclosure of personal information, please feel free to contact us at:\n\n\tAttn: Legal Department\n\t4205 Chapel Ridge Road\n\tLehi, UT 84043\n\tdataprivacy@residentinsure.com</string>

</resources>